http://www.thestampmaker.com/Privacy-policy.aspx

thestampmaker.com
Rubber Stamps Unlimited, Inc.
334 South Harvey St., Plymouth, MI 48170
Phone: (888) 451-7300 | Email: sales@thestampmaker.com
$1 of every Gift Stamp & Monogram, purchased through 12/25/20, goes to Gleaners Community Food Bank of Southeastern Michigan.
0
Design Your StampCustom Stamp DesignerDate Stamp DesignerBand Stamp DesignerRubber StampsTypes of Rubber StampsAddress StampsMonogram StampsDate StampsInspection StampsOffice StampsArt & Logo StampsSignature StampsNotary StampsSeal StampsAlpha-Numeric Band StampsBank StampsWedding StampsGift StampsPopular Stamp FeaturesSelf-Inking StampsPre-Inked StampsWood Rubber StampsPocket StampsSpecial Application StampsQuick Dry StampsFabric StampsStamps for SkinStock Rubber StampsPopular Stock StampsStock Number StampsStock Date StampsSmall Stock StampsSecurity StampsTeacher StampsCOVID-19 StampsInks, Pads and MarkersTypes of InkStamp InkQuick Dry Stamp InkHand & Invisible Stamp InkFabric InkStamp CleanerStamp PadsStamp PadsReplacement Self-Inking Stamp PadsDry Industrial Stamp PadsSpecialty MarkersEmbossersCorporate SealsPersonalized EmbossersNotary Seal EmbossersEngineer Seal EmbossersArchitect Seal EmbossersLandscape Architect Seal EmbossersLand Surveyor Seal EmbossersSeal StampsResourcesGuidesHow-ToCustomer ShowcaseBlog
Orders placed Mon-Fri ship next business day
( exceptions )
( expedited shipping )
Some products take a little longer to ship
XStampers ship in 5 business days. Some colors ship in 10 days and are noted by product.
Quick Dry XStampers ship in 5 business days.
Band Stamps ship in 7 business days.
For orders of 5+ items, we will call/email you if your order will be delayed from our shipping policy.
×
Orders placed by 11am EST with expedited shipping will ship same day (exceptions)
Expedited Shipping Options
USPS Priority Mail Express – arrives 1-2 business days after ordered
UPS Second Day Air – arrives by 5pm 2 business days after ordered
UPS Next
Day Air – arrives 1 business day after ordered
Fedex – requires customer Fedex account number and choice of shipping method
Exceptions
Some products take a little longer to ship.
XStampers ship in 5 business days. Some colors ship in 10 days and are noted by product.
Quick Dry XStampers ship in 5 business days.
Band Stamps ship in 7 business days.
For orders of 5+ items, we will call/email you if your order will be delayed from our shipping policy.
×
Home  ::
Customer Service  ::
Privacy Policy
Sign In
Don't have an account? Create one here.
Email
Password
Remember Me
Forgot Password?
Create An Account
Email
First Name
Last Name
Password
Confirm Password
×
Customer Service
Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting our web site. This Rubber Stamps Unlimited, Inc. privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.
Note, the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.
Collection of Information
We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill your specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.
Cookie/Tracking Technology
The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.
Distribution of Information
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.
Commitment to Data Security
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.
Privacy Contact information
If you would like to opt-out and not receive further communication from us, or if you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:
By E-Mail: sales@thestampmaker.com
By Phone: 888-451-7300
We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
Customer Service Menu
Contact UsFAQVolume DiscountsOrder StatusGuaranteeHow To'sPrivacy PolicyReturn PolicyShipping PolicyTerms and ConditionsSDS Downloads
Sign Up For Our Email List
Get stamp ideas and promotions, plus a line to the newest stamp and embosser products to save you time, money, and frustration.
We do not share your email address or flood your inbox!
Volume Discounts
Large volume orders quoted quickly and competitively! Discounts & Quotes
Next Day Shipping
Orders placed by 11:59pm EST Mon-Fri ship next business day. Some Exclusions Apply
Same Day Shipping
Orders placed by 11 am EST M-F are eligible for overnight shipping! Some exclusions apply
Follow us on...
© 2020 The StampMaker. All rights reserved. Sitemap | About Us | Testimonials
Please Wait...
